Obinna Nnenanya

Software Developer at Andela

Nationality: Nigerian.

State Of Origin: Anambra State,

Local Government: Orumba North LGA,

Sex: Male

E-Mail address: <u>obinnaeye@yahoo.com, obinnaeye@gmail.com, obinna.nnenanya@andela.com</u>

Telephone nos: +234(0)8036223826, +234(0)7056633667,

Contact Address: No 20 Unity, Ajibola Crescent, Alapere, Ketu, Lagos, Nigeria.

Current Location: Lagos-Nigeria. **Date of birth:** 18th Feb, 1985.

Marital status: Married.

Links: https://about.me/nnenanya, <a href="https://about.me/nnenanya, <a href="https://about.me/nnenanya, <a href="https://about.me/nnenanya, <a href="https://about.me/nnenanya, <a

Summary

I am a Software Developer with interests in Big Data, Animations and Machine Learning. I have ample experience in Full-stack web app development, Data Visualisation, Agile Development and Remote Team Work. I have contributed to a few open source projects including Code For Africa (CKAN) and Mozilla (Balrog).

I love to be part of a growing and challenging team.

Education

Free Code Camp

Full Stack Web Development Certification, Computer Software Engineering: 2016 - 2017

National Teachers Institute, Kaduna

PGDE, Education: 2013 - 2013

Nnamdi Azikiwe University

Bachelor of Science (BS), Applied Biochemistry: 2003 - 2007

Experience

Software Developer at Andela

April 2017 - Present

Science Teacher at PPSSC Anambra State

December 2013 - April 2017 (3 years 5 months)

Independent State Director at Abraham Children Foundation - Anambra State (Volunteering)

November 2013 - April 2017 (3 years 6 months)

Field Sales Officer at Etisalat (Sales and Supervision)

June 2013 - March 2014 (10 months)

Hobbies

- Learning new things
- Teaching and Reading
- Graphic designing/drawing
- Playing Table tennis
- Playing Guitar or Piano